Let's first convert this function into a class.
لنحوِّل هذه الدالة إلى فئة أولًا.
Everything inside the constructor function
يوضع أي شيء بداخل دالة المنشئ
is now placed inside a method with the name constructor.
داخل أسلوب باسم المنشئ.
This constructor method will automatically run when
سيعمل أسلوب المنشئ هذا تلقائيًا
a new object is constructed from this class.
عند إنشاء كائن جديد من هذه الفئة.
If any data is needed to create the object,
إذا احتاجت أي بيانات إلى إنشاء الكائن،
then it needs to be included here.
يلزم إدخالها هنا.
So this takes care of creating an object.
لذا فإن ذلك سيهتم بإنشاء أحد الكائنات.
Now the methods that all objects inherit are placed inside the class.
توضع الآن الأساليب التي تكتسبها جميع الكائنات داخل الفئة.
startEngines exists on the prototype explicitly in the pre-class way of writing it.
يوجد بدء المحركات في النموذج النمطي صراحة في طريقة ما قبل إنشاء الفئة من كتابته.
Now, it appears inside the class,
يظهر الآن في الفئة،
but the functionality is exactly the same.
لكن الوظيفة هي نفسها تمامًا.
Also, it looks like startEngines and this constructor method are the same kind of method,
كما يبدو أن بدء المحرك وأسلوب المنشئ ينتميان إلى نوع الأسلوب نفسه،
but the constructor method is not on the prototype, it's a new,
لكن أسلوب المنشئ ليس نموذجًا نمطيًا، بل إنه أسلوب خاص جديد،
special method that exists in a class and is used to initialize new objects.
يوجد في إحدى الفئات ويُستخدم لتهيئة الكائنات الجديدة.
To drive this home, the functionality of these two is exactly the same.
ونؤكد أن وظيفة الاثنين متشابهة تمامًا.
This class syntax is just a nicer way of writing this.
بنية الفئة هذه هي الطريقة الأمتع في كتابة ذلك.
In fact, we create new objects in exactly the same way with this new class syntax.
في الحقيقة، نقوم بإنشاء كائنات جديدة بنفس طريقة بنية الفئة الجديدة هذه.
If you already understand prototypal inheritance,
إذا فهمتم معنى الاكتساب النمطي بالفعل،
then you already have a good understanding of how class and class methods work.
فستفهمون طريقة عمل الفئة وأساليبها جيدًا.